<resources>
    <string name="simple_exception">Exception</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_title">Oh no - What now? 🙁</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_we_need_info">We need the following technical information to help you:</string>
    <string name="simple_close">Close</string>

    <string name="error_dialog_tip_token_mismatch_retry">Please try to force close the app and restart it again. There might have been an incorrect connection to the Nextcloud app.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_tip_clear_storage_might_help">If the issue persists, try to clear the storage of both apps: Nextcloud and Nextcloud Deck to solve this issue.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_tip_database_upgrade_failed">The upgrade of the database failed. Please report the issue and clear the storage to use the app normally.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_tip_clear_storage">You can clear the storage by opening the app info and selecting Storage → Clear storage.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_tip_files_outdated">Your Nextcloud app seems to be outdated. Please visit the Play Store or F-Droid to get the latest version.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_tip_files_force_stop">Something seems to be wrong with your Nextcloud app. Please try to force stop both, the Nextcloud app and the Nextcloud Deck app.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_tip_files_delete_storage">If force stopping them does not help, you can try to clear the storage of both apps.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_timeout_instance">There wasn\'t a response from your server in the given time. Please make sure your instance is running well.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_timeout_toggle">Check your network connection. Sometimes toggling the mobile data or Wi-Fi off and on again can help.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_check_server">The response of your server was not correct. Please check whether you can access the Deck app via web interface.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_check_server_logs">There is an issue with your Nextcloud setup. Please have a look into the server log files.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_check_maintenance">Please check whether your Nextcloud instance is not currently in maintenance mode.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_insufficient_storage">Your Nextcloud instance has no free storage left. Please delete some files to sync your local changes into your cloud.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_redirect">Your server did respond with a HTTP 302 status code, which implies, that you do not have installed the Deck app on your server or something is misconfigured. This can be caused by custom overrides in a .htaccess-file or by Nextcloud apps like OID Client.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_version_not_parsable">We could not determine the version of the server side Deck app. Please make sure it is installed and enabled.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_account_might_not_be_authorized">The account of your Nextcloud app might no longer be authorized.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_user_not_found_in_database">The current user does not match the user we have in our database. If you are using LDAP on your Nextcloud instance, your Nextcloud app might have stored an old user ID.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_capabilities_not_parsable">We could not fetch the capabilities of your server. Please make sure your server is running well and other client apps are able to access Nextcloud.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_attachment_upload_failed">An attachment could not be uploaded. Please try to share it on another way and let us know about this bug.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_tip_disable_battery_optimizations">Please disable all battery optimizations for Nextcloud and the Deck app.</string>

    <string name="error_action_open_deck_info">Open App info</string>
    <string name="error_action_open_network">Network settings</string>
    <string name="error_action_server_logs">Server logs</string>
    <string name="error_action_install">Install</string>
    <string name="error_action_report_issue">Report</string>
    <string name="error_action_open_battery_settings">Battery settings</string>

    <string name="url_fragment_server_logs" translatable="false">/index.php/settings/admin/logging</string>
</resources>
